previewshots.com 2016-01-23

# Snap.com: Delivering Contextual Content And Advertising > Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting online user privacy. In order to ensure your privacy, information we collect is used only in the manner and for the purposes described below. 

We provide this privacy policy so we may inform you about how we collection, use, and disclosure of information on our Site and how our advertising technology (“Technology”) processes information on behalf of the online advertisers, website owners, business partners, and other businesses that use our services (our “Clients”). If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at [privacy@snap.com](mailto:privacy@snap.com). Capitalized terms shall have the meaning designated in the Snap Terms of Service located at http://www.previewshots.com/about/terms, unless specifically defined in this Privacy Policy. All references herein to “we” or “us” refer to Snap Technologies, Inc. (“Snap”). All references to the “site” refer to our website located at [http://www.previewshots.com](http://www.previewshots.com/). 

##### Children's Privacy Policy

Our Site is not directed towards children 13 years of age or under and we do not knowingly collect any information from children 13 years of age or under through the Site or our Technology. 

## Privacy Practices for our Website 

##### Personally Identifiable Information 

We collect Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) from the Snap Website, www.Snap.com, when you choose to provide it to us. PII is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This includes, but is not limited to: name, address, telephone number, mobile number, or email address. For example, you may choose to send us PII about yourself in an email or by completing an online form on this Website in order to access a service such as the SnapShots program. We use this information only to contact you to respond to your inquiry. Once collected, we will store your PII for a reasonable time for record keeping purposes. The information that we store is usually deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business. 

##### Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”) from visitors to this Website. Non-PII is information that cannot by itself be used to identify a particular person or entity, and may include your IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, Internet browsing and usage habits, Internet Service Provider, domain name, the time/date of your visit to this Website, the referring URL and your computer's operating system. We use this information to understand our Website traffic and for maintenance of the Website. 

##### Cookies and Web beacons 

We may use “cookies” and web beacons to help us manage this Website. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. Web beacons (also known as “1X1 pixels” or “clear GIFs”) are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. For more information about cookies and web beacons please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/>. 

##### Third Party Websites 

The Snap Website may contain links to and advertisements for websites operated by third parties whose privacy practices may differ from ours. While we take steps to associate only with reputable entities, Snap cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites. We encourage you to check the privacy policies of all websites that you visit. 

##### Deleting your PII 

If you'd like us to delete any PII that you have provided to us on this Website, please send your request to us at [privacy@snap.com](mailto:privacy@snap.com) and we will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt. 

## Privacy Practices for our Technology

##### Overview of our Technology 

Our Technology collects information about the website(s) that you visit and the advertisements that you see while online. You may encounter our Technology: when we purchase online advertisements on a website that you visit; when one of our Clients purchases online advertisements on a website that you visit; and/or when one of our Clients places one of our web beacons on its website, which you visit. 

We use the information collected by our Technology in order to help make the online advertisements you see more relevant to you, and for ad delivery and reporting purposes. 

### Types of information we collect via our Technology 

##### Personally Identifiable Information

We don't collect Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) via our Technology. 

##### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”) via our Technology, including but not limited to your IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, the URL, the referring URL, Internet Service Provider, and your computer's operating system. 

##### Cookies and Web beacons

Our Technology uses cookies in conjunction with Web beacons in order to help make the online advertisements you see more relevant to you. We also use cookies and web beacons to measure the success of our online advertising campaigns, and the campaigns of our Clients. 

## Controlling the use of your information 

##### Opting out from Cookies

If you'd like to opt-out from having Snap collect your Non-PII in connection with our Technology, please see our opt-out page located at http://www.snap.com/about/opt_out. we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie tells us not to collect your Non-PII to tailor online advertisement campaigns. Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice. 

##### Deleting your PII

Although we don't collect PII via our Technology, if you'd like us to delete any PII that you have provided to us on this Website, please send your request to us at [privacy@snap.com](mailto:privacy@snap.com) and we will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt. 

## Disclosure of Information to Third Parties 

We do not collect PII via our Technology, and we do not sell, rent or share PII collected on the Website with non-affiliated third parties without your consent. We may, however, share your PII with trusted third party contractors who provide services for us. These third party contractors are prohibited from using the information we provide for purposes other than performing services for us. 

We may share Non-PII collected via our Technology with Clients. Similarly, we may enhance the Non-PII collected via our Technology with Non-PII collected from Clients. This information cannot be used to contact or identify any person individually. 

We may disclose your information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. 

Finally, we may transfer information any information we have to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change. 

## Storage of Information and Security

We retain PII collected via the Website for a reasonable time for record keeping purposes. The information that we store is usually deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business. We don't collect PII via the Technology. We retain the Non-PII collected via the Technology for up to 24 months, after which time the information is only stored in aggregate form. 

The security of your information is important to us. We have implemented reasonable security measures to protect the information in our care, both during transmission and once we receive it. This includes, but is not limited to the use of encryption. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about our security practices, please send an email to us at [privacy@snap.com](mailto:privacy@snap.com)

## Changes to this Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy is subject to change. If we make any material or substantive changes in the way that we use the PII collected through this Website, we will post a clear and conspicuous notice of those changes on the Website and in this privacy policy. 

##### General

Third party Internet sites accessible through hyperlinks from this site have their own privacy practices, and Snap has no responsibility or liability for these independent practices. Please review their privacy practices for yourself. 

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy periodically. Any amendments made to this Privacy Policy will be considered effective ten (10) days after the amendments are posted on the site. 

##### Contact Information

If Users have any questions about our services or Privacy Policy, please contact Snap Support, c/o Snap Technologies, Inc., 130 West Union Street, Pasadena, CA 91103 USA. 

Users may also email [privacy@snap.com](mailto:privacy@snap.com) with questions about our Privacy Policy, and info@snap.com with questions about our services. 

_Last Update: May 25, 2011_
